Guide to the History 126 Scrapbooks, 1996-2000
History 126 Scrapbooks, 1996-2000
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
History 126 scrapbooks, 1996-2000.
37-05-2891
Cornell University. Dept. of History.
249 v.
Scrapbooks.
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library.
Student scrapbooks, with annotations, compiled by students in Professor Carol Kammen's History 126 course, documenting the freshman experience for the Classes of 1998, 1999, 2000, 2001, 2002, 2003, 2004, 2005, 2006, and 2007.
BIOGRAPHICAL NOTE
Compilers for Fall 1996 include Michael Belleville, Caryn Caskey, Samantha Cohn, Jeffrey Dayton, Ronnie Fischer, Brian Fulmer, Meredith Page Haff, Severance MacLaughlin, Scott Strazik, and Michael D. Boull.
Compilers for Spring 1997 include Alisha Schmidt, Rion Lucas Weideman, Jessica Mueller, Woon Yin Denise Cheung, Anna Gravino, Jennifer Little, Dorothy Clark, Lisa Liu, Eric T. Wolk, Joshua M. Goldfarb, Scott Weiss, Kimberly Caesar, Brad S. Ackerman, Rory Halperin, and Molly Brenna Gregware.
Compilers for Fall 1997 include Nansen Ng, Mary L. Higgins, Neha Shah, Seana Richardson, Christopher P. Kenaley, Andrew Addotta, Margaret E. Gwin, Peter Bachrach, Jeffrey Tyhach, Nicky Merrill, Keith Epstein, Ayan Mandal, Charles Phillip Yates, Marisa Lizak, Nicole Maria Neroulias, and Lily Liang.
Compilers for Spring 1998 include Brandon Bray, Micaela Chadwick, Claudia C. Hong, David Thomas Myrick, Dan McCoy, Jerry Robert Parmenter, Dianna Power, Lev Kantorovskiy, Paula Ding, Doug Titus, Keith Eisenman, Nick Naum, Karen Klingele, Matthew Hirsch, Chris Jennings, and Amanda Rubenstein.
Compilers from the Classes of 2001 and 2002 (Fall 1998) include Mike Pecorella, David Wasileski, Krista Harwick, Ginny Miles, Alexander J. Ho, Ricky Rahne, Joshua L. Gleis, Jesse Z. Chen, Anita Mark, Debra Newman, Neil Lahiri, Courtney Davis, Shaun Peet, Ho Kum Luen, Brian Weinberg, and David Kozier.
Compilers from the Classes of 2002 and 2003 (Spring 1999) include Michael Bronstein, Joseph Edward Cornell, Nick Della Valle, Julie DeMichele, Adam Hersly, Todd Hilgendorff, Weichun "Chau-Jean" Lin, Abigail Miller, Meredith Silverman, Lesley Slater, Rachel Cohen-Stevens, Stewart Wight, Kari Zarzecki, and Joni Rabiner.
Compilers from the Classes of 2001, 2002, and 2003 (Fall 1999) include Amy Becker, Jordana Beren, Beth Fuller, Matt Jabinsky, Chris Joseph, Rebecca Kaplan, Nadia Klein, Abhishek Mathur, James McGee, Peter McNamara, Molly Morse, John Overton, Regina Rennix, Julia Schneider, Bill Schuerman, Rachel Stecker, and Benjamin E. Wolfe.
Compilers for Spring 2000 include Robin Abraham, Margaret Berthold, Chad Contino, Gail Feder, Rachel Diana Goldstein, Claudio W. Gualtieri, Jennifer Lynn Haupt, Allison Horne, Nathalie Hunt, John-Patrick Benjamin Janowski, Amy Lawrence, Scott McQuade, Kyle O'Brien, Alicia Smith, and Matthew Wise.
Compilers for Fall 2000 include Ben Brickner, Stephen Brooks, Ana Cajina, Robert Carroll, Robert Anthony Chu, Garrett Cox, Maeve Mara Curtin, Theresa R. Fives, Rachel Goldberg, Christina Hynes, Polly Israni, David Lloyd, Steve Lowe, Hilary S. Smith, and Ben Spoonhower.
Compilers for Spring 2001 include Elaine Auyeung, Grace Auyeung, Jill Crispell, Monika Fabriczi, Natalie Gingerich, Molly Harro, Richard Kim, Joanne Lee, Sarah Lindauer, Ivy Moondance Marr, Emily Marx, Justin Nachod, Emily Pollak, John Schuldt, Koh Shimizu, David Shu, and FeiFei Zhu.
Compilers for Fall 2001 include David Armstrong, Brandon J. Gargiulo, Mollye Levy, Joe Long, Jillian Mikolajczyk, Alexander Mikszewski, Chris Mitchell, S. Christopher Mullins, Jason Oswalt, Rich Rohl, Ashley St. Amand, Daniel Schudroff, Daniel Seigerman, Carolyn Kay Smith, Karl Stauderman, and Bethany Tong.
Compilers for Spring 2002 include Adrienne Ashford, Eleanor Bartolomeo Filippone, Erin Finan, James Healy, Deanna Laufer, Yue Monica Li, Marc Marcella, Kimberly O'Hara, Blesserene Punzalan, Joseph Rabinowitz, Kevin Striepe (CD), Matthew Tyhach, and Danielle Yerdon.
Compilers for Fall 2002 include Jonathan Bellante, Daniel Becker, John Costello, ALexis M. Fraser, Edgar Higgins, Kristen Kotran, Jean-Paul LaClair, Justin Manzo, Dan Preston, Colyer Pridgen, Matthew Volner, and Heather Young.
Compilers for Spring 2003 include Christopher Anderson, Amy Elizabeth Brown, Emily Chuk, Susan Dauber, Erin Detweiler, Erik Kronstadt, Sarah LaVallee, Desmond Ling, Sara Lozyniak, Christine McInnis, Katie Regan, Cara Santillo, Gregory Simonds, Alex M. Solomon, Karla Van Duyn, and Kevin Wong.
Compilers for Fall 2003 include Angelina Ang, Elizabeth Bennett, Daniel Brill (CD), Stephanie Chillemi, Steve DeGrow, Brian Lee, Roman Markh, Patrick Morse, Dana Muir, Mariya Nazginova, Brittany Pettitt, Euwyn Poon, Dave Post, Amy Schimpf, Owen Shieh, Shannon Thomson, and Neil Uffner.
Compilers for Spring 2004 include Leah Barad, Thomas Caswell, Diana B. DiBernardo, Keith Dickey (CD), Aditya Didolkar, Brandon Firestone, Andy Lee, Gregory Mak, Ryan Monaghan, Tsipora Nemes, Brian Schimpf, Cindy Sobieski, Christian Tamayo (CD), Shirley Taylor, and Kevin Wong
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
Student scrapbooks, with annotations, compiled by students in Professor Carol Kammen's History 126 course, documenting the freshman experience for the Classes of 1998, 1999, 2000, 2001, 2002, 2003, 2004, 2005, 2006, and 2007 relating to dormitory life, athletics, religious activities, fraternity and sorority rushing, academic life, social events and activities, college costs, food, letters to and from home, and other events characterizing the lives of new college students. Some scrapbooks include critiques by other members of the compiler's class.
SUBJECTS
Names:
Abraham, Robin.; Ackerman, Brad S.; Addotta, Andrew.; Anderson, Christopher.; Ang, Angelina.; Armstrong, David.; Ashford, Adrienne.; Auyeung, Elaine.; Auyeung, Grace.; Bachrach, Peter.; Barad, Leah.; Bartolomeo, Eleanor.; Becker, Amy.; Becker, Daniel.; Bellante, Jonathan.; Belleville, Michael.; Bennett, Elizabeth.; Beren, Jordana.; Berthold, Margaret.; Boull, Michael D.; Bray, Brandon.; Brickner, Ben.; Brill, Daniel.; Bronstein, Michael.; Brooks, Stephen.; Brown, Amanda Lynne.; Brown, Amy Elizabeth.; Caesar, Kimberly.; Cajina, Ana.; Cape, John W.; Carroll, Robert.; Caskey, Caryn.; Caswell, Thomas.; Chadwick, Micaela.; Chalfin, Eric.; Chasalow, Elizabeth.; Chen, Jesse Z.; Chesaniuk, Jenna.; Cheung, Woon Yin Denise.; Chillemi, Stephanie.; Christensen, Lauren.; Chu, Robert Anthony.; Chuk, Emily.; Clark, Dorothy.; Cohen-Stevens, Rachel.; Cohn, Samantha.; Collica, Lawrence.; Contino, Chad.; Cornell, Joseph Edward.; Costello, Abby.; Cox, Garrett.; Crispell, Jill.; Curtin, Maeve Mara.; Dauber, Susan.; Davis, Courtney.; Dayton, Jeffrey.; DeGrow, Steve.; Della Valle, Nick.; DeMichele, Julie.; Detweiler, Erin.; DiBernardo, Diana B.; Dickey, Keith.; Didolkar, Aditya.; Ding, Paula.; Eisenman, Keith.; Epstein, Keith.; Eskenazi, Mark.; Fabriczi, Monika.; Feder, Gail.; Filippone, Lea.; Finan, Erin.; Firestone, Brandon.; Fischer, Ronnie.; Fives, Theresa R.; Fraser, Alexis M.; Fuller, Beth.; Fulmer, Brian.; Gargiulo, Brandon J.; Gingerich, Natalie.; Gleis, Joshua L.; Goldberg, Rachel.; Goldfarb, Joshua M.; Goldstein, Rachel Diana.; Gravino, Anna.; Gregware, Molly Brenna.; Gualtieri, Claudio W.; Gwin, Margaret E.; Haff, Meredith Page.; Halperin, Rory.; Harro, Molly.; Harwick, Krista.; Haupt, Jennifer Lynn.; Healy, James.; Hersly, Adam.; Higgins, Edgar.; Higgins, Mary L.; Hilgendorff, Todd.; Hirsch, Matthew.; Ho, Alexander J.; Hong, Claudia C.; Horne, Allison.; Hunt, Nathalie.; Hynes, Christina.; Israni, Polly.; Jabinsky, Matt.; Janowski, John-Patrick Benjamin.; Jennings, Chris.; Joseph, Chris.; Kammen, Carol, 1937-; Kantorovskiy, Lev.; Kaplan, Rebecca Lynne.; Kenaley, Christopher P.; Kim, Richard.; Klein, Nadia.; Klingele, Karen.; Kotran, Kristen.; Kozier, David.; Kronstadt, Erik.; LaClair, Jean-Paul.; Lahiri, Neil.; Laufer, Deanna.; LaVallee, Sarah.; Lawrence, Amy.; Lee, Andy.; Lee, Brian.; Lee, Joanne.; Levy, Mollye.; Li, Yue Monica.; Liang, Lily.; Lin, Weichun "Chau-Jean."; Lindauer, Sarah.; Ling, Desmond.; Little, Jennifer.; Liu, Lisa.; Lizak, Marisa.; Lloyd, David.; Long, Joe.; Lowe, Steve.; Lozyniak, Sara.; Luen, Ho Kum.; MacLaughlin, Severance.; Mak, Gregory.; Mandal, Ayan.; Manzo, Justin.; Marcella, Marc.; Mark, Anita.; Markh, Roman.; Marr, Ivy Moondance.; Marx, Emily.; Mathur, Abhishek.; McCoy, Dan.; McGee, James A., III.; McInnis, Christine.; McNamara, Peter.; McQuade, Scott.; Merrill, Nicky.; Mikolajczyk, Jillian.; Mikszewski, Alexander.; Miles, Ginny.; Miller, Abigail.; Mitchell, Chris.; Monaghan, Ryan.; Morse, Molly.; Morse, Patrick.; Mueller, Jessica.; Muir, Dana.; Mullins, S. Christopher.; Myrick, David Thomas.; Nachod, Justin.; Naum, Nick.; Nazginova, Mariya.; Nemes, Tsipora.; Neroulias, Nicole Maria.; Newman, Debra.; Ng, Nansen.; O'Brien, Kyle.; O'Hara, Kimberly.; Oswalt, Jason.; Overton, John Daniel, Jr.; Parmenter, Jerry Robert.; Pecorella, Mike.; Peet, Shaun.; Pettitt, Brittany.; Pollak, Emily.; Poon, Euwyn.; Post, Dave.; Power, Dianna.; Preston, Dan.; Pridgen, Colyer.; Punzalan, Blesserene.; Rabiner, Joni.; Rabinowitz, Joseph.; Rahne, Ricky.; Regan, Katie.; Rennix, Regina.; Richardson, Seana.; Rohl, Rich.; Rubenstein, Amanda.; St. Amand, Ashley.; Santillo, Cara.; Schimpf, Amy.; Schimpf, Brian.; Schmidt, Alisha.; Schneider, Julia Katherine.; Schudroff, Daniel.; Schuerman, Bill.; Schuldt, Jon.; Seigerman, Daniel.; Shah, Neha.; Shieh, Owen.; Shimizu, Koh.; Shu, David.; Silverman, Meredith.; Simonds, Gregory.; Slater, Lesley.; Smith, Alicia.; Smith, Carolyn Kay.; Smith, Hilary S.; Sobieski, Cindy.; Solomon, Alex M.; Spoonhower, Ben.; Stauderman, Karl.; Stecker, Rachel.; Strazik, Scott.; Striepe, Kevin.; Tamayo, Christian.; Taylor, Shirley.; Thomson, Shannon.; Titus, Doug.; Tong, Bethany.; Tyhach, Jeffrey.; Tyhach, Matthew.; Uffner, Neil.; Van Duyn, Karla.; Volner, Matthew.; Wasileski, David.; Weideman, Rion Lucas.; Weinberg, Brian.; Weiss, Scott.; Wight, Stewart.; Wise, Matthew.; Wolfe, Benjamin E.; Wolk, Eric T.; Wong, Kevin.; Yates, Charles Phillip.; Yerdon, Danielle.; Young, Heather.; Zarzecki, Kari.; Zhu, FeiFei.; Cornell University. Class of 1998.; Cornell University. Class of 1999.; Cornell University. Class of 2000.; Cornell University. Class of 2001.; Cornell University. Class of 2002.; Cornell University. Class of 2003.; Cornell University. Class of 2004.; Cornell University. Class of 2005.; Cornell University. Class of 2006.; Cornell University. Class of 2007.; Cornell University--Students.; Cornell University--Freshmen.; Cornell University--Students--Religious life and customs.; Cornell University--Athletics.; Cornell University--Rowing.
Subjects:
Women college students.; History--Study and teaching--United States.; College students--Social life and customs.; College students' writings, English--New York (State)--Ithaca.; College students--Sports.; College students--Attitudes.; College students--Sexual behavior.; College students--Conduct of life.; College students--Economic conditions.; September 11 Terrorist Attacks, 2001.
Form and Genre Terms:
Scrapbooks.
INFORMATION FOR USERS
Access Restrictions:
Box 34a (Koh Shimizu journal) is restricted to permission of the donor until 2032.
CONTAINER LIST
- Scrapbooks Fall 1996 (Box 1)
  - Michael Belleville (Box 1)
  - Michael D. Boull (Box 1)
  - Brian Fulmer (Box 1)
  - Meredith Page Haff (Box 1)
- Scrapbooks Fall 1996 (Box 2)
  - Caryn Caskey (Box 2)
  - Ronnie Fischer (Box 2)
- Scrapbooks Fall 1996 (Box 3)
  - Samantha Cohn (Box 3)
  - Jeffrey Dayton (Box 3)
  - Severance MacLaughlin (Box 3)
  - Scott L. Strazik (Box 3)
- Scrapbooks Spring 1997 (Box 4)
  - Alisha Schmidt (Box 4)
  - Rion Lucas Weidman (Box 4)
- Scrapbooks Spring 1997 (Box 5)
  - Woon Yin Denise Cheung (Box 5)
  - Jessica Mueller (Box 5)
- Scrapbooks Spring 1997 (Box 6)
  - Dorothy Clark (Box 6)
  - Anna Gravino (Box 6)
  - Jennifer Little (Box 6)
  - Lisa Liu (Box 6)
- Scrapbooks Spring 1997 (Box 7)
  - Kimberly Caesar (Box 7)
  - Joshua Goldfarb (Box 7)
  - Scott Weiss (Box 7)
  - Eric T. Wolk (Box 7)
- Scrapbooks Spring 1997 (Box 8)
  - Brad S. Ackerman (Box 8)
  - Rory Halperin (Box 8)
  - Molly Brenna Gregware (Box 8)
- Scrapbooks Fall 1997 (Box 9)
  - Nansen Ng (Box 9)
  - Mary L. Higgins (Box 9)
  - Neha Shah (Box 9)
  - Seana Richardson (Box 9)
  - Christopher P. Kenaley (Box 9)
- Scrapbooks Fall 1997 (Box 10)
  - Andrew Addotta (Box 10)
  - Margaret E. Gwin (Box 10)
  - Peter Bachrach (Box 10)
- Scrapbooks Fall 1997 (Box 11)
  - Jeffrey Tyhach (Box 11)
  - Nicky Merrill (Box 11)
- Scrapbook Fall 1997 (Box 12)
  - Lily Liang (Box 12)
- Scrapbooks Fall 1997 (Box 13)
  - Keith Epstein (Box 13)
  - Nicole Maria Neroulias (Box 13)
- Scrapbooks Fall 1997 (Box 14)
  - Ayan Mandal (Box 14)
  - Charles Philip Yates (Box 14)
  - Marisa Lizak (Box 14)
- Scrapbook Spring 1998 (Box 15)
  - Brandon Bray (Box 15)
  - Micaela Chadwick (Box 15)
- Scrapbooks Spring 1998 (Box 16)
  - Claudia C. Hong (Box 16)
  - Dan McCoy (Box 16)
  - Jerry Robert Parmenter (Box 16)
- Scrapbook Spring 1998 (Box 17)
  - David Thomas Myrick (Box 17)
- Scrapbooks Spring 1998 (Box 18)
  - Dianna Power (Box 18)
  - Lev Kantorovskiy (Box 18)
  - Paula Ding (Box 18)
  - Doug Titus (Box 18)
  - Keith Eisenman (Box 18)
- Scrapbooks Spring 1998 (Box 19)
  - Nick Naum (Box 19)
  - Karen Klingele (Box 19)
- Scrapbooks Spring 1998 (Box 20)
  - Matthew Hirsch (Box 20)
  - Chris Jennings (Box 20)
  - Amanda Rubenstein (Box 20)
- Scrapbooks Fall 1998 (Box 21)
  - Mike Pecorella (Box 21)
  - David Wasileski (Box 21)
  - Krista Harwick (Box 21)
- Scrapbooks Fall 1998 (Box 22)
  - Ginny Miles (Box 22)
  - Alexander J. Ho (Box 22)
  - Ricky Rahne (Box 22)
  - Joshua L. Gleis (Box 22)
- Scrapbooks Fall 1998 (Box 23)
  - Jesse Z. Chen (Box 23)
  - Anita Mark (Box 23)
  - PCL/ACT Diary with EE (Box 23)
- Scrapbooks Fall 1998 (Box 24)
  - Debra Newman (Box 24)
  - Neil Lahiri (Box 24)
  - Courtney Davis (Box 24)
- Scrapbook Fall 1998 (Box 25)
  - Jesse Z. Chen Journal, August-December 1998 (Box 25)
- Scrapbook Fall 1998 (Box 26)
  - Shaun Peet (Box 26)
- Scrapbooks Fall 1998 (Box 27)
  - Ho Kum Luen (Box 27)
  - Brian Weinberg (Box 27)
  - David Kozier (Box 27)
- Scrapbooks Spring 1999 (Box 28)
  - Michael Bronstein (Box 28)
  - Joseph Edward Cornell (Box 28)
  - Nick Della Valle (Box 28)
  - Julie DeMichele (women's soccer--photocopy) (Box 28)
  - Adam Hersly (Box 28)
  - Todd Hilgendorff (Box 28)
  - Wiechun "Chau-Jean" Lin (Box 28)
  - Abigail Miller (Box 28)
  - Joni Rabiner (Box 28)
  - Meredith Silverman (Box 28)
  - Lesley Slater (Box 28)
  - Rachel Cohen-Stevens (Box 28)
  - Stewart Wight (Box 28)
  - Kari Zarzecki (women's lacrosse--photocopy) (Box 28)
- Scrapbooks Fall 1999 (Box 29)
  - Amy Becker (Box 29)
  - Jordana Beren (Box 29)
  - Matt Jabinsky (Box 29)
  - Christopher J. Joseph (Box 29)
  - Rebecca Lynn Kaplan (Box 29)
  - Nadia Klein (Box 29)
  - James A. McGee III (Box 29)
  - Molly Morse (Box 29)
  - John Daniel Overton, Jr. (Box 29)
  - Regina Rennix (Box 29)
  - Julia Katherine Schneider (Box 29)
  - Bill Schuerman (Box 29)
  - Rachel Stecker (Box 29)
  - Benjamin E. Wolfe (Box 29)
- Scrapbooks Fall 1999 (Box 30)
  - Beth Fuller (Box 30)
  - Abhishek Mathur (Box 30)
  - Peter McNamara (Box 30)
- Scrapbooks Spring 2000 (Box 31)
  - Robin Abraham (Box 31)
  - Maggie Berthold (Box 31)
  - Chad J. Contino (Box 31)
  - Gail Feder (Box 31)
  - Jennifer Lynn Haupt (Box 31)
  - Allison Valley Horne (Box 31)
  - John Patrick Benjamin Janowski (Box 31)
  - Amy Lawrence (Box 31)
  - Kyle Michael O'Brien (Box 31)
  - Alicia Smith (Box 31)
  - Matthew Wise (Box 31)
- Scrapbooks Spring 2000 (Box 32)
  - Rachel Diana Goldstein (Box 32)
  - Claudio Gualtieri (Box 32)
  - Nathalie Hunt (Box 32)
  - Scott McQuade (Box 32)
- Scrapbooks Fall 2000 (Box 33)
  - Ben Brickner (Box 33)
  - Stephen Brooks (Box 33)
  - Ana Cajina (Box 33)
  - Robert Carroll (Box 33)
  - Robert Anthony Chu (Box 33)
  - Garrett Cox (Box 33)
  - Maeve Mara Curtin (Box 33)
  - Theresa R. Fives (Box 33)
  - Rachel Goldberg (Box 33)
  - Christina Hynes (Box 33)
  - Polly Israni (Box 33)
  - David Lloyd (Box 33)
  - Steve Lowe (Box 33)
  - Hilary S. Smith (Box 33)
  - Ben Spoonhower (Box 33)
- Scrapbooks Spring 2001 (Box 34)
  - Elaine Auyeung (Box 34)
  - Grace Auyeung (Box 34)
  - Jill Crispell (Box 34)
  - Monika Fabriczi (Box 34)
  - Natalie Gingerich (Box 34)
  - Molly Harro (Box 34)
  - Richard Kim (Box 34)
  - Joanne Lee (Box 34)
  - Sarah Lindauer (Box 34)
  - Ivy Moondance Marr (Box 34)
  - Emily Marx (Box 34)
  - Justin Nachod (Box 34)
  - Emily Pollak (Box 34)
  - Jon Schuldt (Box 34)
  - David Shu (Box 34)
  - FeiFei Zhu (Box 34)
- Scrapbook--RESTRICTED Spring 2001 (Box 34a)
  - Koh Shimizu (Box 34a)
- Scrapbooks Fall 2001 (Box 35)
  - David Armstrong (Box 35)
  - Brandon J. Gargiulo (Box 35)
  - Mollye Levy (Box 35)
  - Joe Long (Box 35)
  - Jillian Mikolajczyk (Box 35)
  - Alexander Mikszewski (Box 35)
  - Chris Mitchell (Box 35)
  - S. Christopher Mullins (Box 35)
  - Jason Oswalt (Box 35)
  - Rich Rohl (Box 35)
  - Ashley St. Amand (Box 35)
- Scrapbooks Fall 2001 (Box 36)
  - Daniel Schudroff (Box 36)
  - Daniel Seigerman (Box 36)
  - Carolyn Kay Smith (Box 36)
  - Karl Stauderman (Box 36)
  - Bethany Tong (Box 36)
- Scrapbooks Spring 2002 (Box 37)
  - Adrienne Ashford (Box 37)
  - Eleanor Bartolomeo (Box 37)
  - Amanda Lynne Brown (Box 37)
  - Lea Filippone (Box 37)
  - Erin Finan (Box 37)
  - Marc Marcella (Box 37)
  - Yue Monica Li (Box 37)
  - Kimberly O'Hara (Box 37)
  - Blesserene Punzalan (Box 37)
  - Joseph Rabinowitz (Box 37)
- Scrapbooks Spring 2002 (Box 38)
  - Eric Chalfin (Box 38)
  - Lawrence Collica (Box 38)
  - Deanna Laufer (Box 38)
  - Kevin Striepe (Box 38)
  - Matthew Tyhach (Box 38)
  - Danielle Yerdon (Box 38)
- Scrapbooks Fall 2002 (Box 39)
  - Daniel Becker (Box 39)
  - Jonathan Bellante (Box 39)
  - John W. Cape (Box 39)
  - Elizabeth Chasalow (Box 39)
  - Jenna Chesaniuk (Box 39)
  - Lauren Christensen (Box 39)
  - Abby Costello (Box 39)
  - Alexis M. Fraser (Box 39)
  - Edgar Higgens (Box 39)
  - Kristen Kotran (Box 39)
  - Jean-Paul La Clair (Box 39)
  - Sara Lozyniak (Box 39)
  - Justin Manzo (Box 39)
  - Dan Preston (Box 39)
  - Colyar Pridgen (Box 39)
  - Matt Volner (Box 39)
  - Heather A. Young (Box 39)
- Scrapbooks Spring 2003 (Box 40)
  - Amy Elizabeth Brown (Box 40)
  - Emily Chuk (Box 40)
  - Susan Dauber (Box 40)
  - Erin Detweiler (Box 40)
  - Erik Kronstadt (Box 40)
  - Sarah LaVallee (Box 40)
  - Desmond Ling (Box 40)
  - Mark Lombardi (Box 40)
  - Christine McInnis (Box 40)
  - Katie Regan (Box 40)
  - Cara Santillo (Box 40)
  - Alex M. Solomon (Box 40)
  - Karla Van Duyn (Box 40)
  - Kevin Wong (Box 40)
- Scrapbooks Spring 2003 (Box 41)
  - Christine McInnis, Oversized Supplement (Box 41)
- Scrapbooks Spring 2003 (Box 42)
  - Christopher V. Anderson (Box 42)
  - James Healy (Box 42)
- Scrapbooks Fall 2003 (Box 43)
  - Angelina Ang (Box 43)
  - Elizabeth Barclay Bennett (Box 43)
  - Stephanie Rose Chillemi (Box 43)
  - Steve DeGrow (Box 43)
  - Brian Lee (Box 43)
  - Roman Markh (Box 43)
  - Dana Francis Muir (Box 43)
  - Euwyn Poon (Box 43)
  - Amy Schimpf (Box 43)
  - Owen Shieh (Box 43)
  - Shannon Thomson (Box 43)
  - Neil Uffner (Box 43)
- Scrapbooks Fall 2003 (Box 44)
  - Daniel Brill (Box 44)
  - Patrick Morse (Box 44)
  - Mariya Nazgovina (Box 44)
  - Brittany Pettitt (Box 43)
  - David Post (Box 44)
- Scrapbooks Spring 2004 (Box 45)
  - Leah Barad (Box 45)
  - Thomas Caswell, Fall 2013 - placed with Spring 2004 scrapbooks due to limited box space. (Box 45)
  - Diana B. DiBernardo (Box 45)
  - Keith Dickey (Box 45)
  - Aditya Didolkar (Box 45)
  - Brandon Firestone (Box 45)
  - Andy Lee (Box 45)
  - Gregory Mak (Box 45)
  - Ryan Monaghan (Box 45)
  - Tsipora Nemes (Box 45)
  - Nick Nieh (Box 45)
  - Brian Schimpf (Box 45)
  - Cindy Sobieski (Box 45)
  - Christian Tamayo (Box 45)
  - Shirley Taylor (Box 45)
  - Kevin Wong (Box 45)
  - Devon Goodrich (Box 46)